Jesus… she's stunning.
What noble house is that?
Why the hell would someone like
her
come to a filthy mine?
She's here for me.
Severin, come on, man.
If you knew someone like that,
you wouldn't be here
busting your ass with us.
Elowen Morellan, heir of House Morellan,
pays her respects to Lord Severin.
The Four Great Houses...
sending their heir
to find a miner.
What do you want?
My lord… I've admired you for so long.
I want to marry you.
In exchange, I offer
everything House Morellan has.
I'm just a miner.
There's nothing here worth that kind of price.
My lord, I know you're tired of it all.
You want a peace, quiet life...
If marriage isn't what
you want, I understand.
Just...
let me stay.
Let me serve you.
I already have a fiancée.
You filthy peasant!
Do you know who you're refusing?!
Sandero!
No. No, no, no.